In the next couple of videos, we're going to be looking at the details of the Cool
在接下来的几个视频中，我们将看到Cool的详细信息
operational semantics going over the semantics of each individual kind of
操作语义学复习每一种个体类型的语义
expression. We'll start with easy ones and work our way up to the more complicated
表达式。我们将从简单的问题开始，逐步发展到更复杂的问题
ones. So the easiest rules are the rules for the constants in Cool. So the value
一个。所以最简单的规则是Cool中常量的规则。所以它的价值
true, the expression true I should say, evaluates to a Boolean with the value true
TRUE，我应该说表达式TRUE的计算结果是一个值为TRUE的布尔值
And it doesn't modify the store so the store is unchanged because it doesn't do
它不会修改存储，因此存储不会改变，因为它不会
any updates obviously And there's a corresponding rule for false And integers
任何明显的更新，对于False和整数都有相应的规则
are very, very similar so if a integer expression, integer literal i will
非常非常相似，所以如果一个整数表达式，整数文字I将
evaluate to, and integer object with the value i and again the store is not
求值为，并且整型对象的值为i，并且存储也不是
modified by such evaluation. And finally, strings if a, if s is a string literal of
被这样的评价所修正的。最后，字符串，如果a，如果s是的字符串文字
length n, then it will be evaluated by the string object of which the properties n
长度n，则它将由其属性为n的字符串对象求值
and the string constant s. The evaluation of identifiers is very straightforward,
和字符串常量s。标识符的计算非常简单，
given that we have both in environment in the store. So to evaluate an identifier
考虑到我们在商店的环境方面都有。因此，要计算标识符
and this would be a variable lane y x or y or for What do we do? Well first we look
这将是一个可变的通道y，x或y，或者我们该怎么做呢？好的，我们先来看看
up in the environment where that identifier is stored so now we give us
在存储该标识符的环境中，所以现在我们给我们
back a memory location l. So by in this case And then we look up in the store what
返回内存位置l。在这种情况下，然后我们在商店中查找
the value is at that memory locations, So, we use the same memory location here as an
该值位于内存位置，因此，我们在这里使用与
argument to the store to get back the value that, that, that variable currently
参数传递到存储区，以获取当前，那个，那个变量的值
has And notice I just have a reference, this is a read of memories so this is
注意到我只有一个参考，这是对记忆的读取，所以这是
loading, I think it was loading the value of the variable. This does not affect the
加载，我想它是在加载变量的值。这不会影响
store so the store is the same before and after. This is just looking at the value
商店，所以商店前后是一样的。这只是看看它的价值
of the variable not updating the variable. The expression self just evaluates to the
不更新变量的变量的。表达式self仅计算为
self object. So, this is a place where we just make use of the fact that the self
自我客体。所以，在这个地方，我们只是利用了这样一个事实，即自我
object is part of the environment so let's just copy them over here as the result of
对象是环境的一部分，因此让我们将它们复制到这里，因为
expression and that was again that the store is unaffected by evaluation of self.
也就是说，商店不受自我评价的影响。
Now let's see of a more slightly more complicated evaluation is evaluated, in
现在让我们看一下更复杂的评估，在
particular the assignment expression. So an assignment consists of two parts, an
特别是赋值表达式。因此，一个作业由两个部分组成，一个
identifier that is being updated and an expression that is going to give us the
正在更新的标识符和将为我们提供
new value. So for example, just to remind you we might have something like x gets
新的价值。举个例子，提醒你们一下，我们可能会有类似于x得到的东西
one + one so one + one here would be the expression e and x would be the identifier
1+1，所以这里的1+1是表达式e，x是标识符
All right? And so in order to evaluate the assignment, the first thing we have to do
好的?所以为了评估作业，我们要做的第一件事
is we have to know what value we're going to be writing into the identifier. So what
我们必须知道要写入标识符的值是什么。那又怎样
is the, what is the update we're going to perform? So the first thing to do is to
我们要执行的更新是什么？所以首先要做的就是
evaluate e, okay? And notice here that e is evaluated in the same environment so it
评估一下e，好吗？请注意，这里的e是在相同的环境中计算的，所以它
has the same three components here, and here, all right? So it just says the first
在这里和这里都有相同的三个组成部分，好吗？所以它只是说第一个
thing we do is we run e. Okay. That will give us back a new value. We're going to
我们要做的就是运行e。好的。这将带给我们一个新的价值。我们要去
get back on value b excuse and possibly an updated score so you can arbitrate a piece
回到价值b的借口上，可能还有一个更新的分数，这样你就可以仲裁一张棋子了。
of code. You could yourself have assignment statements in it so the story
代码。你可以自己在里面写赋值语句，所以这个故事
that we get out might be different. Alright, so e produces the value of e and
我们出去的方式可能会有所不同。好的，所以e产生e的值，
an update store s1 And now it's actually due to assignment, what do we do? Well we
更新存储S1，现在它实际上是由于分配，我们该怎么办？嗯，我们
have to know what memory location was supposed to update so we look up the
必须知道应该更新的内存位置，所以我们查找
memory location for id and that would give us some location else of id. And then we
存储id的位置，这会给我们提供id的其他位置。然后我们
modify the store with the new, we modify the store at that point with the new value
用新的值修改存储，我们就用新值修改该点的存储
so we replace the location l, i, d or we update the value of l, i, d to be the
所以我们替换位置l，i，d，或者将l，i，d的值更新为
value of e, the value b and we do that in store s1 which gives us a new store s2.
e的值，值b，然后我们在存储s1中这样做，这给了我们一个新的存储s2。
And I've noticed. That s2 is the store that results from the evaluation of e,
我注意到了。S2是从E的求值得到的存储，
okay? So after we do the assignment, the assignment returns the value b which is of
好吧?所以在我们进行赋值之后，赋值返回值b，它是
course the value of a, of running e. And, it returns the updated store s2. Next,
当然，运行e.的a的值，并且它返回更新的存储S2。接下来，
let's talk about the operational rule for addition. So, to evaluate e1+e2, what we
我们来谈谈加法的运算规则。所以，要评估e1+e2，我们
are going to do? So, first we evaluate e1 And notice that is done in the same
会做什么呢？因此，首先我们评估E1，并注意在相同的
context as the context of the entire e xpression, okay? So the components the
上下文作为整个表达的上下文，好吗？所以这些组件
context here for evaluating one are exactly the same as the components for the
此处用于评估一个的上下文与
overall expression e1 + e2. So when we evaluate e1 it's going to give us a value
整体表达式e1+e2。所以当我们评估E1时，它会给我们一个值
of e1 and it's also going to give us an updated store s1 And then we're going to
它还将为我们提供更新后的商店S1，然后我们将
evaluate e2 and notice here And I think context is different. The soft objects in
评估e2并注意这里，我认为上下文是不同的。中的软对象
the environment are the same; same but now we're running e2 in the new store s1. And
环境是相同的，但是现在我们在新存储S1中运行e2。和
what does its saying is that if e2 has, has assignments or variable references in
它是怎么说的呢？如果e2中有赋值或变量引用
it those assignments and variable references have to be done on the store
如果这些赋值和变量引用必须在存储上完成
that resulted from running e1, okay? So, it's very important that we get that any
那是用E1造成的，好吗？所以，非常重要的是，我们要得到
side effects would happen in running e1 are visible or that are seen by the
在运行E1过程中将发生的副作用是可见的或由
expression e2. So we run e2 in this environment, we're going to get the value
表达式e2。所以我们在这个环境中运行e2，我们将获得
of e2 and the updated store s2 And then the result of the entire expression is
e2和更新后的存储s2的结果，则整个表达式的结果为
going to be b1 + b2 and the results it store will be the store s2. And notice
将是b1+b2，并且它存储的结果将是存储s2。并请注意
here how the stores tell you the order in which you have to evaluate the
下面是商店如何告诉您您必须按照什么顺序评估
expressions. So because e1 is evaluated in the same store as the overall expression
表情。因此，因为E1在与整体表达式相同的存储中求值
that tells you that e1 has to be evaluated first. And then because e2 is evaluated in
这告诉您必须首先评估E1。然后因为e2的求值是在
the store that's produced by e1, that tells you that e1, e2 excuse me, has to be
由e1生产的商店，它告诉你，e1，e2打扰一下，必须是
evaluated after you've evaluated e1 and then the fact that. S2 is the result of
在你评估了E1之后评估，然后事实是。S2是以下各项的结果
the whole thing. It tells you that E2 is also the last thing that you evaluate
整件事。它告诉您E2也是您评估的最后一件事
during the execution of this particular expression. Okay, let's take a look at the
在执行此特定表达式期间。好，我们再来看一下
statement block and just a variety here on the change my colors. How are we going to
声明挡路和刚刚这里的一个品种就换了我的颜色。我们要怎么做呢？
evaluate the, a statement block of statements e1 through en, okay, so, while
评估一下，语句E1到EN的一个语句挡路，好的，所以，虽然
this is semantics, this is that we should run, I mean order beginning of e1 and the
这是语义，这是我们应该运行的，我的意思是订单开始于E1和
results of the entire execution will be the, let's say the value of the entire
整个执行的结果就是，比方说整个
block with the value of the last expression. And this, this rule just says
最后用挡路的价值表达。而这个，这个规定就是说
that. So, first, we evaluate e1 and also it's done on the same store as the overall
那。因此，首先，我们评估E1，并且它也是在与整体商店相同的商店中完成的
expressio n as it tells you it has to come first and that produces a new store s1 and
表达式n，因为它告诉你它必须首先出现，这会产生一个新的存储s1和
the value b1. Okay And then e2 is evaluated in the store s1 and it produces
值b1。好的，然后e2在存储s1中求值，它产生
the store s2 and so on And then expression en is evaluated in the store sn - one and
存储s2以此类推，然后在存储sn-one中计算表达式en，并且
it produces a value of bn and an updated store s (N). Okay? And then the result of
它产生的值为bn和更新后的存储s(N)。好吧?然后结果是
the whole thing is the value of vn and also the updated store s (N) and this
整件事就是vn的值，还有更新后的商店s(N)和这个
tells you, this would really tell you the order which had to evaluate the sub
告诉你，这会告诉你评估潜艇的顺序
expressions. The dependencies here on the store of course you do evaluate e1 and
表情。当然，这里存储上的依赖项计算的是e1和
then e2 and then e3 and so on so you have to do them to net order to get the side
然后是e2，然后是e3，依此类推，因此您必须将它们设置为净订单才能获得边框
effects to get. You know the side effects in the correct order for all of these
要得到的效果。你知道所有这些药的副作用顺序是正确的
expressions And furthermore, it also tells you the only value that you're going to
表达式，此外，它还告诉您要计算的唯一值
keep is the value vn. Notice that none of the other values that are produced here
Keep是值vn。请注意，此处生成的任何其他值
are used for anything. They don't appear anywhere else in the rules. Let's think
可以用来做任何事情。他们不会出现在规则中的其他任何地方。让我们想一想
what we've learned so far and do a small example. So we want to know what happens
我们到目前为止所学的内容，并做一个小例子。所以我们想知道会发生什么
when we evaluate the block. X gets assigns seven + five, that's the first statement
当我们评价挡路的时候。X GET赋值7+5，这是第一个语句
and the second and the last statement in the block, is just the expression four.
而挡路中的第二句话，也是最后一句话，就是表达式四。
And the first thing we have to do is to say what the context did and which we are
我们要做的第一件事是说出上下文做了什么，我们是什么
going to evaluate this and the context consists of three parts. There'll be a
我们要对此进行评估，上下文由三个部分组成。会有一个
self object and in this case it doesn't really matter what's in the self object
Self对象，在这种情况下，Self对象中的内容实际上并不重要
because self is not referred to in the program and so it won't play any role in
因为程序中没有提到Self，所以它不会在
the evaluation. But we, we still need it so there still be, there'll be some self
评估。但是我们，我们仍然需要它，所以仍然会有，会有一些自我
object out there just won't get used and Now, in the new environment which tells us
外面的物体就是不会被使用，而现在，在新的环境中，这告诉我们
the locations where all the free variables in the programs. So, we'll just need a
程序中所有自由变量的位置。所以，我们只需要一个
place for x is going to be stored and so s will be stored in some location l And then
将存储x的位置，因此s将存储在某个位置l，然后
we know our memory content is, where our store is and let's just say that at l we
我们知道我们的记忆内容是，我们的商店在哪里，我们可以这样说，在l，我们
have initially the value zero, okay? So now we can use our rules to run this
初始值为零，好吗？所以现在我们可以用我们的规则来运行
program or to evaluate thi s program. I'm going to make this line here much longer
计划或评估此计划。我要把这条线排得更长一些
And recall that, that evaluation of block consist of the evaluation of the, all the
请记住，对挡路的评价包括对所有
statements within the block. Okay, so the first one is going to be s gets seven+5
挡路内部的声明。好的，第一个是s得到7+5
and that will be evaluated in the same environment as the overall expression. So,
它将在与整体表达式相同的环境中求值。所以,
we have up here. So the same context excuse me and I should say I often slip
我们在这上面有。所以在同样的背景下，请原谅，我应该说我经常滑倒
and I realize and say environment for the entire left hand side of one of these
我意识到其中一个的整个左手边的环境
judgments. I'll try to be consistent. And just use environment for the, for the
判断。我会努力做到始终如一。只需将环境用于，用于
second components of the context often in the literature people call the entire
语境的第二个组成部分通常在文学中被人们称为整体
thing on the left hand side of the environment that's why they make this
在环境的左手边的东西，这就是为什么他们做这个
mistake but you know for this instead of notes I'm trying to be consistent the
我错了，但是你知道，这个而不是笔记，我试着保持一致
entire, all the components on left hand side together are called the context and
整个，左侧的所有组件一起称为上下文和
the environment is just the second component. The mapping from variables to
环境只是第二个组成部分。变量到变量的映射
their locations Anyway coming back to the example, The first statement in the block
他们的位置反正回过头来举个例子，挡路里的第一句话
is s gets seven+5 alright. And then we're going to have the second statement as
就是S得到7+5好的。然后我们将有第二个声明，即
well. And we know that the self object and the environment won't change but we don't
井。我们知道自我对象和环境不会改变，但我们不会
know what the store will be. The store might be different so I'll leave the store
知道商店会是什么样子。商店可能不一样，所以我要离开商店了
empty for now and we'll figure that out later and we're going to be evaluating the
现在是空的，我们稍后会弄清楚这一点，我们将评估
expression four. Okay, so this is the structure of the evaluation now in
表达式四。好的，这就是现在评估的结构
progress. We should look at, at this first statement trying to make some forward
进步了。我们应该看看，在这第一个声明中，试图做出一些前瞻
progress on that one. So, to evaluate the assignment, what do we have to do? Well,
在这个问题上取得了进展。那么，要评估作业，我们需要做些什么呢？井,
the very first thing we have to do is we have to evaluate the right hand side so
我们要做的第一件事就是评估右手边
we're going to have the context for that is going to be the same And the context
我们将会有相同的背景和背景
we've been looking at all on because it's the first thing that's actually going to
我们一直在看，因为这是第一件真正要做的事情
happen is to evaluate Seven + five, okay? And now, I'm leaving a little space down
就是评估7+5，好吗？现在，我在下面留下一点空间
here for the rest of the assignment role which we're not going to fill in just yet.
这里是睡觉的分配角色，我们现在还不打算填写。
Now to evaluate the plus expression we have to evaluate the first express ion and
现在要计算加号表达式，我们必须计算第一个表达式离子和
the second expression, okay? And so, how do we do that? Well, we know, finally, I
第二个表情，好吗？那么，我们如何做到这一点呢？嗯，我们知道，最后，我
think how to do that because we're finally down and we're going to have a single
想一想怎么做，因为我们终于下来了，我们将有一首单曲
integer there and that we already have a rule for, okay and so an integer
这里有一个整数，我们已经有了一个规则，好的，所以是一个整数
literal evaluates to institute your object, okay And inside that object is
文本求值来建立您的对象，好的，在该对象内部是
just about the value, okay. And the store is unmodified All right? And then
只是关于价值，好的。而且商店是原封不动的，好吗？然后
similarly for the other argument here, Okay. So the five will also evaluate to an
这里的另一个论点也是如此，好的。因此这五个国家也将评估为
integer object with the value of five and the store will be unmodified okay so
值为5的整数对象，存储将不会被修改，所以
that's the two sum expressions of this edition and so now we can fill in the
这是本版的两个求和表达式，现在我们可以填写
results here so to take the contents of the two integers we'll add them. That will
结果在这里，为了获得两个整数的内容，我们将它们相加。那将会
also be integer object so we're going to have the integer object twelve. And the
也是整数对象，所以我们将有整数对象12。以及
store has not been changed, okay? So the, the store that we get out of here happens
店铺没变，好吗？所以，我们离开这里的商店发生了
to be the same as the store that went in just because this expression had no
与进店的商店一样，就因为这句话没有
assignments in it, okay? And now we're ready to do the assignment. Okay. So how
把任务放进去，好吗？现在我们准备好做作业了。好吧。那么是怎么做到的呢？
do we do that? Well, we have to form a new store. Alright, so we're going to have a
我们要这么做吗？嗯，我们得开一家新店。好的，那么我们将会有一个
new store which will the L gets zero with the value of l. Number which way, my
将L取值为零的新商店。数字朝哪个方向，我的
notation went here, I think it's the number comes first and we're going to put
记号放在这里，我想数字放在第一位，我们要把
twelve in the location l and of course, that's store was just equal to the store
12个在位置l，当然，那家店正好等于那家店
where l has the value twelve, okay And so now, what happens down here and we do the
这里l的值是12，好的，现在，这里发生了什么，我们做
assignment and we get out The new value. Okay so, the value of the right hand side
赋值，然后我们得到新值。好的，那么，右手边的值
is twelve and we have a new store where the location l has twelve, all right? So
是12，我们有一家新店，位置l是12，对吗？所以
now we're going to evaluate the second statement in the block and that will be
现在我们来评估挡路中的第二个陈述，那就是
done in the store where l has the location twelve and of course this is just an
在l的位置是12的商店里做的，当然这只是一个
integer And so that will evaluate to the integer constant of four, the integer
整数，因此将计算为整数常量4，即整数
value excuse me, 4or integer object containing, the integer object with the
值，对不起，4或整数对象包含，整数对象带有
value four and our store. And it's just going to fit not quite, all right? And
价值四和我们的商店。只是不太合身，好吗？和
that's then the result of the entire evaluation . So, this block will produce
这就是整个评估的结果。那么这个挡路呢就会产生
the value four, an integer object with the value four and an updated store where
值4、值为4的整数对象和更新后的存储，其中
location l has the value twelve. So, the next expression I would like to take a
位置l的值为12。所以，下一个表达式我想用一个
look at is the if, then, else expression and to evaluate if, then, else what do we
请看IF，THEN，ELSE表达式，并计算IF，THEN，ELSE我们要做什么
do? Actually there should be if, then, else. See of course, so evaluating if,
做?实际上应该有如果，那么，其他的。当然看到了，所以评估是否，
then, else as well. First we have to evaluate the, the predicate and it's done
那么，其他的也一样。首先我们要评估一下这个谓词，然后就完成了
in the same store, the same context as the overall expression and if the result is
在同一存储区中，返回与整个表达式相同的上下文，并且如果结果为
true If the, if the Boolean predicate returns the value true. Then we want to
如果布尔谓词返回值TRUE，则为TRUE。那么我们想要
evaluate just the true branch and not the false branch so that's why you only see
只评估真分支，而不是假分支，这就是为什么您只能看到
here, evaluation of e2 and e3 isn't mentioned anywhere and just know here that
这里，任何地方都没有提到e2和e3的评估，这里只知道
the predicate may have side effects and so e2 is evaluated in whatever store that e1
谓词可能有副作用，因此在任何存储e1中评估e2
produces And then the results of the entire expression is the value of e2.
生成，然后整个表达式的结果是e2的值。
Okay, that's v and also just the final store is produced by running the then
好的，这就是v，最后的存储也是通过运行
branch. And there is a symmetric rule for what happens if the predicate evaluates
布兰奇。如果谓词求值，则会发生什么情况有一个对称规则
the false. In that case, you would evaluate e3 and not e2. Next we'll take a
虚假的。在这种情况下，您将计算e3而不是e2。接下来我们要做一个
look with what happens with while loops and cool. So there are two cases. First if
看看While循环和酷发生了什么。所以有两个案例。首先，如果
the predicate of the while loop evaluates the false, okay. Well, in this case the
WHILE循环的谓词计算FALSE，好的。嗯，在这种情况下，
loop body is not going to execute, alright so the first thing we do is we evaluate
循环体不会执行，所以我们要做的第一件事就是计算
the predicate and that's done in the same context as the evaluation of the overall
谓词和它是在与整体评估相同的上下文中完成的
expression and if the predicate is false then we exit the loop and so the results
表达式，如果谓词为假，则退出循环，因此结果
of the loop is void. The value void and just whatever store resulting from
是无效的。值无效以及由此产生的任何存储
evaluating the predicate. The other possibility is that the predicate
评估谓词。另一种可能性是谓词
evaluates the true. So here we evaluate the predicate again in the same context as
计算TRUE。因此，在这里，我们在相同的上下文中再次计算谓词，如下所示
the overall loop. And if the predicate evaluates the true then we're going to run
整个循环。如果谓词的计算结果为真，那么我们将运行
the loop audio once. Okay. So we'll evaluate the loop audio and also that's
循环音频一次。好吧。所以我们将评估循环音频，也就是
done in this, in whatever store results from evaluating the predicate. Evaluating
在评估谓词得到的任何存储结果中执行此操作。评估
the loop audio is g onna give us a value of v and a new store s2 and then what we
循环音频将给我们一个值v和一个新存储s2，然后我们
need to do is we need to go back around and execute the loop again and how can we
需要做的是，我们需要返回并再次执行循环，我们如何才能
do that? Well, we're really just running the whole loop in the new context. So, the
这样做吗？嗯，我们实际上只是在新的背景下运行整个循环。所以呢，这个
next thing we do is we evaluate the entire loop. Right in the new store So, after I
接下来我们要做的是评估整个循环。就在新店里，所以，在我
execute the loop by, loop body one time, then we go around and just evaluate the
执行循环，循环主体一次，然后我们遍历并只计算
loop again And when this may run for zero or more iterations, alright. And when I
再次循环，当这可能运行零次或多次迭代时，好的。当我
finally terminate, if it terminates, it will produce it will produce a new store
最后终止，如果它终止，它将产生它将产生一个新的存储
s3 evaluated while because always produced the value of a void. And then what we'll
S3求值时，因为始终生成空值。然后我们要做的是
produce for the entire loops, for the entire expression is the value void and
为整个循环生成，为整个表达式生成的值为void和
the update and store s3. The next interesting expression to take a look at
更新并存储S3。下一个要看的有趣的表达式
is the let expression. So recall how, what this looks like so let and cool has a
是let表达式。所以回想一下，这看起来是什么样子，让和酷有一个
variable thing declared and it's type and an initializer which is optional so this
声明的变量事物及其类型，以及一个可选的初始值设定项，因此此
is the value that the identifier will be initialized to and then the expression in
是标识符将初始化为的值，然后是
which that new variable is available. And so how do we evaluate this? Well first,
新变量是否可用。那么，我们如何评估这一点呢？那么首先呢，
we're going to evaluate the initial value of the, of the new variables. So we
我们要计算新变量的初值。所以我们
evaluate e1 and as usual that's done in the initial store it produces possibly
评估E1，并像往常一样，在它可能产生的初始存储中完成
modified store. And now the question is, what are going to, what's going to be the
修改过的商店。现在的问题是，什么会，什么会是
context here for the evaluation of e2 for the body of the latter? And so it seems
这里的上下文是为后者的身体评估e2吗？看起来就是这样
clear that it's going to involve s1 because it has all the updates from e2 but
很明显，它将涉及S1，因为它有来自e2的所有更新，但是
it also has to have this new identifier in it. And so how are we going to do that?
它还必须在其中包含此新标识符。那么我们要怎么做呢？
So, what we want is to have a new environment e but with new binding of ID
因此，我们想要的是有一个新的环境e，但具有新的ID绑定
to refresh location. So, we're introducing a new variable. Remember that the
若要刷新位置，请执行以下操作。所以，我们引入了一个新的变量。请记住，
environment has tracked all the free variables so this is one situation where
环境已经跟踪了所有自由变量，所以这是一种情况
you should going to extend the environment e with the new binding, alright. And that
您应该使用新的绑定来扩展环境e，好的。那就是
location, the location for the new variable has to be a fresh location. We
位置，则新变量的位置必须是新位置。我们
don't want to conflict with any other memory locations we are already using.
不想与我们已经使用的任何其他内存位置冲突。
Okay And so, we're going to allocate a new memory location for the variable And then
好的，我们将为变量分配一个新的内存位置，然后
the store, the new store will also will be like as one as we said we have to include
商店，新商店也会像我们说的那样，我们必须包括
all the, the values for s1 But also, we can have these new location for the
所有的，S1的值，而且，我们还可以将这些新位置
variable and that's going to have the initial value of the variable e1. To
变量，它会有变量E1的初始值。至
express that we need a new location, we're going to introduce a new operation on the
表示我们需要一个新的地点，我们将在
store which gives us a new fresh location. So new lo applied to a store it's just
它给了我们一个新的新鲜地点。所以新的LO申请了一家商店，只是
going to give us some location that isn't being used by the store. So, the store has
会给我们一些没有被商店使用的位置。所以，这家商店有
a domain where it's a mapping from locations to values and we'll just pick
一个域，其中它是从位置到值的映射，我们只需选择
some new location that isn't in the current list of locations within the store
不在商店内当前位置列表中的某些新位置
and that will be the one returned or that will be one, that will be the one returned
这将是退还的，或者那将是退还的，那将是退还的
by new lo. Okay, so new lo if you can think of As modeling the memory allocation
以新的方式。好的，如果您可以将新loo看作是对内存分配进行建模的话
function in the runtime system. So, then, here we can write out the rule. So, this
函数在运行时系统中运行。那么，我们可以在这里写出规则。那么这个呢，这个
is the most complicated rule we seen so far. So, I'll just take a moment to walk
是我们到目前为止看到的最复杂的规则。所以，我就花点时间走一走
through it All right? So, the first thing we do is we evaluate e1, the initializer
一切顺利吗？因此，我们要做的第一件事是评估初始值设定项E1
for the new variable, okay? So just like before, this is done in the same context
新的变量，好吗？因此，就像以前一样，这是在相同的上下文中完成的
as the overall expression and this is going to give us a value for e1 and an
作为整体表达式，这将为我们提供e1和
updated store, all right? Then in the updated store, using the updated store
更新商店，好吗？然后在更新后的存储中，使用更新后的存储
here we find an unused location, l new. Okay And then we're going to create a
在这里我们找到了一个未使用的位置，l新的。好的，然后我们要创建一个
store where that new location has, has the value of e1. So we're going to store the
存储在新位置所在位置的值为E1。所以我们要存储
value of e1 at that new location. We're going to update the store s1 to reflect
该新位置的E1的值。我们将更新商店S1以反映
that and further more we're going to extend our environment with the new
此外，我们还将使用新的
identifier which will be stored at this new location and this is the context then.
将存储在这个新位置的标识符，这就是上下文。
Okay, with this updated environment in store in which we evaluate the body of the
好的，有了这个更新的环境，我们在其中评估了
lab which will produce the value b2 and possible update in store s2 and those are
Lab将在存储s2中生成值b2和可能的更新，它们是
the results of the overall expression.
整体表达式的结果。